Varun Tyagi

Dehradun, Uttarakhand, India

varuntyagi228@gmail.com

9310148941

linkedin.com/in/varun-tyagi-149428281

Summary

I AM A FIRST YEAR STUDENT AT DIT UNIVERSITY DEHRADUN.

MY BRANCH IS BTECH CSE WITH SPECIALIZATION IN -- FULL STACK DEVELOPER AND DEVOPS. ALWAYS I AM READY TO LEARN NEW THINGS,

MOSTLY I LOVE DOING CODING IN WEB DEVELOPMENT FIELD.

Member at CGC Boot sequence

Experience

Web Development Intern

CodSoft

Dec 2023 - Present (2 months)

Excited to be the part of codsoft virtual internship program in web development as main domain . This will be a great experience and learning for me .

Member

DIT University CGC Club Sep 2023 - Present (5 months)

Education

DIT UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Full Stack Developer and Devops 2023 - Present

MCL Saraswati Bal Vidya Mandir

Skills

JavaScript • C (Programming Language) • Blogging • Coding • Engineering • C++ • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)